[
  {
    "status": "success",
    "results": 18,
    "data": {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "_id": "5fd95343f7510d4f0788db10",
          "type": "advanced java class design",
          "question": "Can a static interface method be marked final?",
          "answer": "No"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fd95343f7510d4f0788db12",
          "type": "io",
          "question": "Buffered reader syntax is while(reader.readline()!=null). What will happen?",
          "answer": "It will print null if there are even number of lines"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fd97530cf88366c50f18686",
          "type": "jdbc",
          "question": "An int variable is assigned to an executeQuery command. What will be the output?",
          "answer": "It will not compile."
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fd98206e9db474fb1b6000a",
          "type": "functional programming",
          "question": "public functional interface chew {} // what will be the output",
          "answer": "Does not compile. There is no \"functional\" modifier in Java."
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fd98423e9db474fb1b6000b",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "BasicFileAttributeView.setTimes(null, null, null); // what will be the output ?",
          "answer": "It will leave the BasicFileAttributes date and time values unchanged."
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fd9849be9db474fb1b6000c",
          "type": "concurrency",
          "question": "service.submit(()-> selectWinner(i)); // What is wrong with this code ?",
          "answer": "submit uses a callable or runnable in the form of a lambda and will not take any parameters"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fd98687496a5c7be4b64e9e",
          "type": "generics",
          "question": "given a list of int values without using  generics and an enhanced for loop for(Number num :  list) System.out.print(num) what will be the output ?",
          "answer": "It will not compile. To make it compile replace Number with Object.",
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda6d341d71301be6f3f9fa",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "Which Java version was NIO released in ?",
          "answer": "Java 1.4"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda6ef89482690024616b6c",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "NIO API was intended as a replacement for ....",
          "answer": "java.io.streams"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda6f9b7ef9c70024fa38d0",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "NIO.2 API is actually a replacement for",
          "answer": "java.io.File class"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda70597ef9c70024fa38d1",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "Which interface is the primary entry point for working with the NIO.2 API?",
          "answer": "java.nio.file.Path interface"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda712c7ef9c70024fa38d2",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "_______________ is a is a special file within an operating system that serves as a reference or pointer to another file or directory.",
          "answer": "symbolic link"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda71937ef9c70024fa38d3",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "you can create an instance of a Path interface using a static method available in the ________factory class",
          "answer": "Paths"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda72437ef9c70024fa38d4",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "Why is Path an interface and not a class ?",
          "answer": "The reason why Path is an interface and not a class is that creating a file or directory is considered a file systemâ€“dependent task in NIO.2."
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda72dd7ef9c70024fa38d5",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "_______ base file systems are case sensitive, while ______-based file systems are not",
          "answer": "Linux, Windows"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda736995c9bb0024737726",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "java.nio.file.Files  class's primary purpose is to operate on instances of______objects",
          "answer": "Path"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda73fd95c9bb0024737727",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "Which classes are often composed primarily of static methods that operate on a particular class.?",
          "answer": "Helper or utility classes"
        },
        {
          "_id": "5fda74a995c9bb0024737728",
          "type": "nio2",
          "question": "Helper classes are focused on ________________, whereas factory classes are focused primarily on __________.",
          "answer": "manipulating or creating new objects from existing instances, object creation"
        }
      ]
    }
  }
]
